Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- General subject files, 1924 -- 1993; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.003; 23.65 Linear Feet
  - Certificate of the Secretary of Environmental Affairs on draft environmental report of Interstate 93/Rt. 16, 1979; MS055.003.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Public meeting: 93/16 environmental impact statement, 1976; MS055.003.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - I93/Rt. 16 interchange reevaluation, 1987; MS055.003.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Finding of no significant impact: proposed improvements to the Interstate 93/Rt. 16 interchange in Medford, Mass., 1980; MS055.003.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Financing MBTA operating costs: alternatives for the future, 1989; MS055.003.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Proposed improvements to the Interstate 93/Rt. 16 interchange in the city of Medford, Mass., 1988; MS055.003.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Analysis of reasonably available control measures in the Boston region - summary of case studies, 1981; MS055.003.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Alewife urban design inventory report, 1977; MS055.003.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Alewife open space, MS055.003.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Replacement of the Alewife Bridge, 1978; MS055.003.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Appendix A: responsiveness survey, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass., 1986; MS055.003.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - An evaluation for reclamation of Blair Pond and Wellington Brook for anadromous fish, 1990; MS055.003.018.00003 (Box 18)
    Date is approximate
  - Remote sensing 20 years of change in Middlesex County, Mass., 1951 -- 1971; MS055.003.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Water: a resource you can help restore, 1970; MS055.003.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Elements in negotiating stream flows associated with Federal projects, 1979; MS055.003.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Water pollution equipment and environmental studies, 1979; MS055.003.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - National water quality inventory, 1975; MS055.003.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Massachusetts water resouce coalition river basin planning program: Massachusetts water supply systems, 1983; MS055.003.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Department of Environmental Quality Engineering Division of Water Pollution Control proposed regulations: public hearing draft, 1983; MS055.003.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Groundwater management, Mystic River basin, Massachusetts, Sec. 3.03, 1973; MS055.003.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Summary of municipal actions for groundwater Protection in the New England/New York Region, 1988; MS055.003.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Great Meadows hydrology and land use study, 1970; MS055.003.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Great Meadows hydrology and land use study, 1970; MS055.003.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Spy Pond, a diagnostic study, 1981; MS055.003.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Environmental protection agency support manual: waterbody surveys and assessments for conducting use attainability analyses, 1983; MS055.003.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Massachusetts water supply policy statement, 1978; MS055.003.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Site assessment, Dundee Park properties, Woburn, Mass., 1982; MS055.003.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Storet user handbook, overview chapter 1, MS055.003.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Superfund remedial response program, 1983; MS055.003.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Inventory and analysis of existing well data for East and North Woburn, Mass., 1981; MS055.003.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Evaluation of the hydrology and groundwater quality of East and North Woburn, Mass: appendices A, B, D, E, F, 1982; MS055.003.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Proposed pond reconstruction at Sheehy Industrial Park, Woburn, Mass., 1982; MS055.003.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Undercover Park, Woburn, Mass: supplemental final environmental impact report, 1987; MS055.003.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Planning workshops to develop recommendations for a groundwater protection strategy: appendices, 1980; MS055.003.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Infiltration/inflow analysis of existing sewerage system, Lexington, Mass., 1978; MS055.003.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Report of the southeastern New England study: a strategy for balanced development and protection of water and related land resources in eastern Massachusetts and Rhode Island, 1975; MS055.003.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Regional report on growth policy, 1976; MS055.003.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Perspectives on growth, 1977; MS055.003.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - A preliminary working annotated bibiliography of major water and related land resource studies in southeastern New England, phase 1, 1971; MS055.003.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Water quality, 1978 -- 1980; MS055.003.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - The 208 planning process, 1975; MS055.003.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Citizens' Advisory Committee: groundwater III, 1982; MS055.003.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Field investigations of uncontrolled hazardous waste sites, 1982; MS055.003.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Background and summary of the Massachusetts Department of Public Health's draft carcinogen policy, MS055.003.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Water conservation alternative: literature review and analysis of experience, 1981; MS055.003.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Metropolitan District Commission water watch, summer, 1981; MS055.003.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Potential fringe-parking sites in the Northwest Corridor, 1980; MS055.003.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Inwood Office Park, Woburn, Mass., draft environmental impact report, vol. 1, 1987; MS055.003.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Draft preliminary work plan: immediate action and field investigations, Woburn, Mass., 1981; MS055.003.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Fish, 1971 -- 1990; MS055.003.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Erosion, 1971 -- 1990; MS055.003.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Ducks and geese, 1980 -- 1988; MS055.003.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Water conservation, 1978 -- 1981; MS055.003.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Bicycle routes, 1979 -- 1989; MS055.003.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Acid rain, 1984 -- 1993; MS055.003.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Foundations/funding, 1966; MS055.003.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Energy, MS055.003.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Water pamphlets, 1976 -- 1989; MS055.003.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Balanced fransportation for the city: the Institutional imperative, 1973; MS055.003.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Red Line extension, environmental analysis, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights, Alewife transportation advisory group worksheet, MS055.003.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Alewife area employee survey, 1976; MS055.003.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16: design public hearing, 1984; MS055.003.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16: technical memoranda, MS055.003.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 correspondence, 1975 -- 1988; MS055.003.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Transportation improvement program 1987-1991, 1986; MS055.003.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Draft negative declaration: proposed improvements to the Interstate 93/Rt. 16 interchange, 1978; MS055.003.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memorandum 9-3, 1988; MS055.003.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memorandum 9-3, 1988; MS055.003.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memorandum 9-3, 1988; MS055.003.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Woburn well study, 1980; MS055.003.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Record of decision: Industri-plex, Woburn, 1987; MS055.003.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Summary of remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass., 1986; MS055.003.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Summary of remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass.: appendix A, 1986; MS055.003.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Summary of remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass.: appendix B, 1986; MS055.003.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Summary of remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass.: tables, 1986; MS055.003.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Summary of remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex site, Woburn, Mass.: figures, 1986; MS055.003.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Evaluation of hydrogen sulfide concentration at residential and commercial sites surrounding a Woburn construction area, 1977; MS055.003.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Woburn environmental studies feasibility study, phase 2 report, draft #2, 1985; MS055.003.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Woburn environmental studies phase 2 investigation plan, 1983; MS055.003.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Comments on remedial action alternatives for the Woburn Industri-plex site, 1985; MS055.003.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Floodplan and wetlands aAssessment, Woburn Industri-plex 128 Superfund site, 1986; MS055.003.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - The Woburn health study, 1984; MS055.003.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - Press release: W. R. Grace indictment, 1987; MS055.003.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Final work plan, supplemental remedial investigation/feasibility study, Wells G and H site, Woburn, Mass., 1987; MS055.003.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - Supplemental final environmental impact report, Inwood Office Park, Woburn, Mass., 1989; MS055.003.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - Draft suburban industrial/office park reconaissance report, 1980; MS055.003.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Interim report: water resource task force on environmental reorganization, MS055.003.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - Report to Woburn Conservation Commission on flood plains and wetlands zoning, 1973; MS055.003.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1, Woburn, Mass., volume 3: appendices A and B, 1986; MS055.003.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1, Woburn, Mass., volume 3: appendices A and B, 1986; MS055.003.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1, Woburn, Mass., volume 3: appendices A and B, 1986; MS055.003.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - Permits, 1974 -- 1978; MS055.003.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Habitat course material, 1988; MS055.003.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Materials for course, MS055.003.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Winter course, 1989; MS055.003.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - The environmental quality of the Mystic River Basin, 1970; MS055.003.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed nationwide urban runoff case study, 1982; MS055.003.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Report to town of Arlington on diagnostic/feasibility study of Hill's Pond, Arlington, Mass., 1986; MS055.003.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Spy Pond: phase 2 restoration, draft environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project: main report, 1982; MS055.003.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project: summary, 1982; MS055.003.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project: appendix A, 1982; MS055.003.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project: appendices B-E, 1982; MS055.003.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Wellington Station Area development: final environmental impact statement, 1981; MS055.003.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Final areawide waste treatment management plan, environmental impact statement, 1979; MS055.003.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts outdoors: technical report, 1976; MS055.003.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts outdoors, statewide comprehensive outdoor recreation plan, 1977; MS055.003.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts scenic and recreational rivers, 1979; MS055.003.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts scenic and recreational rivers, 1982; MS055.003.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - Report to the Massachusetts Special Commission on Highways, 1982; MS055.003.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - Red Line new market demand study/summary report, 1977; MS055.003.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Minuteman area transit study: draft feasibility report, phase 1, 1977; MS055.003.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Revised program for mass transportation, 1977; MS055.003.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Revised program for mass transportation, 1978; MS055.003.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Funds for transit: a report to the Governor and the Great and General Court, 1970; MS055.003.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - Transportation plan for the Boston region: long-range element (draft), 1979; MS055.003.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - Boston transportation improvement program, northwest corridor (draft), 1977; MS055.003.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - Transportation improvment program, northwest corridor (draft), 1979; MS055.003.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - 128: moving toward the year 2000, 1985; MS055.003.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - Truck traffic: environmental impact, 1972; MS055.003.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - Feasibility study for resoration of Spy Pond, 1982; MS055.003.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - Feasibility study for resoration of Spy Pond, 1982; MS055.003.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - Draft areawide waste treatment management plan, part 1 volume 3, 1978; MS055.003.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - 314 CMR 4.00 Massachusetts surface water quality standards, MS055.003.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Massachusetts water supply policy, 1977; MS055.003.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Massachusetts water supply policy, 1977; MS055.003.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Town of Arlington facilities planning supply study, 1986; MS055.003.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - Town of Arlington facilities planning supply study, 1986; MS055.003.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Interstate 93 joint transportation study, 1980; MS055.003.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Interstate 93 joint transportation study, 1980; MS055.003.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - Unmetered areas: infiltration/inflow analysis, Medford, Mass., 1980; MS055.003.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - Horn Pond water quality survey part A, 1976; MS055.003.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - Upper Mystic Lake: nationwide urban runoff program case study draft report, 1980; MS055.003.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - Arlington Office Park final environmental impact report, 1982; MS055.003.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - Arlington Office Park final environmental impact report: maps, 1982; MS055.003.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - Proposed new Interstate 93-Woburn interchange: environmental assessment/draft environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1 vol. 1, 1986; MS055.003.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1 vol. 1, 1986; MS055.003.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1 vol. 2, 1986; MS055.003.021.00015 (Box 21)
    First of two folders
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1 vol. 2, 1986; MS055.003.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - Great Meadows, 1955 -- 1979; MS055.003.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - Great Meadows, 1980 -- 1990; MS055.003.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - Guidance material for the preparation of environmental documents, 1982; MS055.003.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - Draft EPA water quality standards handbook, 1982; MS055.003.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - Ecological study of the Great Meadows, Arlington and Lexington, Mass., 1970; MS055.003.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - Stewardship manual for Lexington conservation land, MS055.003.021.00022 (Box 21)
  - Wetlands analysis of Great Meadows, 1989; MS055.003.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - The last billion years of the geological history of the town of Lexington, 1984; MS055.003.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - Proposals for hydrology and land-use study of Great Meadows, 1969; MS055.003.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - Planning board report on Article 49 of the warrant for the 1968 annual town meeting (Lexington), MS055.003.021.00026 (Box 21)
  - Fottler Avenue, MS055.003.021.00027 (Box 21)
  - Local sources feasibility study, 1989; MS055.003.021.00028 (Box 21)
  - MRWA comments on draft environmental impact statement/environmental report, Rt. 2/Alewife Brook Parkway, 1987; MS055.003.021.00029 (Box 21)
  - Great Meadows hydrology and language use study, 1970; MS055.003.021.00030 (Box 21)
  - Results of pump test, Arlington Reservoir/Great Meadows area, 1980; MS055.003.021.00031 (Box 21)
  - Great Meadows diary, 1989; MS055.003.021.00032 (Box 21)
  - Groundwater supply feasibility study Arlington Reservoir/Great Meadows area, 1980; MS055.003.021.00033 (Box 21)
  - Sickle Brook Dam at Fottler Avenue feasibility study, 1981; MS055.003.021.00034 (Box 21)
  - Report on subsoil investigations for Great Meadows study, Arlington-Lexington, Mass., 1970; MS055.003.021.00035 (Box 21)
  - Great Meadows newsclippings, 1969 -- 1989; MS055.003.021.00036 (Box 21)
  - Proposal for an ecological study of the Great Meadows of Lexington, Mass., 1990; MS055.003.021.00037 (Box 21)
  - Final environmental impact report, MBTA Alewife Station, appendix D: traffic, 1984; MS055.003.021.00038 (Box 21)
  - Inwood Office Park, Woburn, Mass., draft environmental impact report, volume 1, 1987; MS055.003.021.00039 (Box 21)
  - Screech owl and crow, 1984 -- 1990; MS055.003.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Recommended 208 area map, MS055.003.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - East Arlington development and open space study overview memorandum, phase 1: framework, 1980; MS055.003.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Arlington, Mass. comprehensive plan memoranda, 1972; MS055.003.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Report of conditions in Spy Pond, Arlington, Mass.: a historical synopsis, 1973; MS055.003.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Weeds and eutrophication, 1971 -- 1989; MS055.003.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Contamination in municipal water supplies, 1986; MS055.003.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Environmental management report, 1985; MS055.003.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Groundwater protection strategy, 1983; MS055.003.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - Probable high ground-water levels in Massachusetts, 1981; MS055.003.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Proposed Alewife local roadway improvements, 1983; MS055.003.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Earthcorps, 1979; MS055.003.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Arlington, Mass.: comprehensive town plan report, 1962; MS055.003.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - The public trust doctrine: a primer for the 1980s, 1984; MS055.003.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Mystic River Basin report, 1977; MS055.003.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - The Mystic River Basin: a preliminary report, 1977; MS055.003.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Alewife revitalization, 1979; MS055.003.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Town of Belmont traffic study, Rt. 2/Alewife development, 1985; MS055.003.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Alewife urban design study, 1977; MS055.003.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - Alewife urban design alternatives report, 1977; MS055.003.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - Spy Pond, 1971 -- 1980; MS055.003.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - Spy Pond, 1964 -- 1979; MS055.003.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Spy Pond, 1966 -- 1986; MS055.003.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Soil conservation service national engineering handbook: hydrology, 1972; MS055.003.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Soil conservation service national engineering handbook: hydrology, 1972; MS055.003.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - Soil conservation service national engineering handbook: hydrology, 1972; MS055.003.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Urban stormwater pollutant loadings, 1980; MS055.003.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Proposal for engineering services in Mystic River Watershed urban runoff project, 1979; MS055.003.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Publications of the technical services branch, 1989; MS055.003.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Joint planning case studied: Metropolitan Area Planning Council, 1975; MS055.003.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Draft environmental impact report: control of aquatic vegetation in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, 1977; MS055.003.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Massachusetts wildlife, 1982; MS055.003.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Report of the Special Commission Relative to Determining the Adequacy of Water Supply in the Commonwealth, 1978; MS055.003.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Report of the Special Commission Relative to Determining the Adequacy of Water Supply in the Commonwealth, 1979; MS055.003.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - MBTA Alewife Station interim access: final environmental impact feport, 1984; MS055.003.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - MBTA Alewife Station interim access: final eEnvironmental impact report, 1984; MS055.003.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - City of Medford, infiltration/inflow analysis, 1980; MS055.003.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Boston Metropolitan planning area report, part 3, volume 2, 1975; MS055.003.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1, volume 4, appendices C-G, 1986; MS055.003.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Wells G and H site remedial investigation report part 1, volume 4, appendices C-G, 1986; MS055.003.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Alewife Center: final environmental impact report volume 1, 1987; MS055.003.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Alewife Center: supplemental final environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Alewife Center: supplemental final environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Draft report on characterization of residuals, 1987; MS055.003.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - Adopt-a-stream workbook, 1987; MS055.003.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - Sickle Brook Dam at Fottler Avenue feasibility study, 1981; MS055.003.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Undercover Park, Woburn: supplemental final environmental impact report appendices, 1987; MS055.003.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Undercover Park, Woburn: supplemental final environmental impact report appendices, 1987; MS055.003.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Mystic River Basin report, appendix A, 1977; MS055.003.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - Mystic River Basin report, appendix B, 1977; MS055.003.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Environmental notification form: Winchester, 1982; MS055.003.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - Local growth policy handbook, MS055.003.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Hydraulic survey of the Aberjona River and operation of the Aberjona River Commission, 1973; MS055.003.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Proposed Alewife roadway improvements, 1984; MS055.003.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - Revised final findings by Massachusetts Water Resource Authority on the secondary treatment facilities plan/environmental impact report for Boston Harbor, 1990; MS055.003.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Draft interim report on flows and loads, 1986; MS055.003.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Growth management techniques, 1978; MS055.003.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Mill Brook Linear Park, 1976; MS055.003.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Mill Brook responsiveness summary, 1980; MS055.003.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Finding of no significant impact, 1985; MS055.003.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project, appendix A, 1982; MS055.003.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project, appendices B-F, 1982; MS055.003.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Upper Mystic Lake Watershed urban runoff project summary, 1982; MS055.003.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Watershed decisions: the case for watershed protection in Massachusetts, 1989; MS055.003.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan: draft interim best management practices report, 1989; MS055.003.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Hazardous waste management regulations for Massachusetts: phase 1 discussion draft, 1981; MS055.003.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Preliminary water quality survey of Horn Pond, Woburn, Massachusetts, 1973; MS055.003.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Final environmental impact report, Sheehy Industrial Park, 1984; MS055.003.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Teaching, 1977 -- 1978; MS055.003.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - East Arlington development and open space study, 1981; MS055.003.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - East Arlington development and open space study, 1981; MS055.003.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - East Arlington development and open space study: technical proposal, 1979; MS055.003.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - East Arlington development and open space study: summary report, 1981; MS055.003.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - East Arlington development and oipen space study, 1979; MS055.003.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Conservation plan for Arlington, draft 3, MS055.003.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Mystic nationwide urban runoff program sampling program, MS055.003.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Trees of the Horn Pond area, 1974; MS055.003.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Environmental notification form: Stoneham, 1983; MS055.003.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Streambank protection guidelines, 1983; MS055.003.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Report on Mill Brook, 1970; MS055.003.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - 1971 cleanup, MS055.003.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Cleanups, 1970 -- 1977; MS055.003.024.00014 (Box 24)